Color Mixer
     by Leocarbon
https://leocarbon.github.io
    realleocarbon@gmail.com

Color Mixer is licensed under

The MIT License (MIT)

Copyright (c) 2012 ~ 2014 Leocarbon

Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy
of this software and associated documentation files (the "Software"), to deal
in the Software without restriction, including without limitation the rights
to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or sell
copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is
furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions:

The above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be included in
all copies or substantial portions of the Software.

THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED "AS IS", WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR
IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY,
FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE
AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER
LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM,
OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN
THE SOFTWARE.

Color Mixer is open source!
http://github.com/leocarbon/Color-Mixer
Use it, mod it, share it (as open source).
Just don't change the license.

-----------------------------------------------------------------------------
version.txt

Past versions, like a history book.


Last Updated 3.2.14 @ 3.0.1 v 2.0.4

Build #0014

3.0.1 (3.2.14)
 - Updated links, licenses and removed unused code.

3.0.0.1 (7.4.13)
 - Font fix (added font files)

3.0.0 (6.11.13)
 - Processing 2 
   -Updated library & syntax
 - Multiple source files with 'tabs'
   - Now using functions with care
 - Lots of bug fixes
   - Scroll() fix
 - GUI
   - Once again, repositioned stuff
   - Added more buttons, including 'reset', 'randomColor', 'invertColor', 'refresh'
   - Bigger size(800,800)
   - Bigger rect(550,550)
   - User-friendly color displaying inside the rectangle
   - Tabs, including software information in the 'About' tab
     - license & blog links moved to 'About' tab
 - More.
   - This might be my last update, because Color Mixer will be on a programming contest!
   - More, Color Mixer will be embedded in Color Utility, currently in development with Java/Processing.
   - You can check out the daughter project here: [https://github.com/leocarbon/cu]
   - Thanks to everybody supportive until this time.

2.0.2 (3.2.13)
 - Processing 2.0b7 syntax support
 - Minor error fixes

2.0.1 (9.10.12)
 - Minor Auto clear bug fixed
   
2.0.0 (9.10.12)
 - Major Breakthrough!!!
   - Minor errors fixed
     - Copyright version updated
     - Release number added
     - brightness to alpha
     - Fixed broken blog link
     - Removed some text in the bottom corner
   - NOW WE HAVE NUMBER INPUT!!!
     - Brought from version 0.2.a0 (4.14.12)
     - Four text input boxes
     - NUI™
       - Number User Interface
   - Graphics
     - Repositioned the UIs
     - Bigger output
       
1.1.6 (8.26.12)
 - Added Scroll™ feature
   - Choose a color you like with scrolling!
   - Control/Command+S
 - Minor adjustments to version notes

1.1.5 (8.25.12)
 - Fixed gray screen bug in MacOSX
 - Minor changes to README.txt
 
1.1.4 (8.25.12)
 - Added licence picture
 - Patch for version notes
   
1.1.3 (8.24.12)
 - Works with Processing 2.0 [developers]
 - We are working on an Android app!
 - Now works with Linux
 - Edited the README
   
1.1.2 (7.8.12)
 - Version Notes Edit
 - Electric Mango Blog ad (my blog)
 - Removed color saving debug code
   
1.1.1
 - Seperate variables for colors (red, green, blue, alpha)
 - Now supports ControlP5 0.7.5
 
1.1.0 v 0.7.2 (6.10.12)
 - Edited the version (added ControlP5 version) 
 - Lowered the slider for a better look
   
1.0.0 v 0.7.2 (5.12.12)
 - Released with Naver Blog and Blogger
  
0.4.rc4 (5.9.12)
 - Open Source license
 - More code commenting
 - Ready to release!!!
   
0.4.rc3 (5.3.12)
 - Now press Contol(Command)+R to reset
   
0.4.rc2 (5.3.12)
 - Removed red, green, blue shortcut keys
 - Removed debug code
   
0.4.rc1 (4.30.12)
 - Reduced file size (a little)
   
0.4.rc0 (4.30.12)
 - Shortcut keys feature
   - Press control+n to reset
   - Press command+n to reset (Mac OS X)
   - Press control+r for color red
   - Press command+r for color red (Mac OS X)
   - Press control+g for color green
   - Press command+g for color green (Mac OS X)
   - Press control+b for color blue
   - Press command+b for color blue (Mac OS X)
     
0.3.rc0 (4.27.12)
 - Fixed Escape key quit bug
 - Commenting for code
  
0.2.b5 (4.20.12)
 - Added copyright message
   
0.2.b4 (4.18.12)
 - Added definition for bars under customer request
   
0.2.a3 (4.17.12)
 - Added new Mac OS X icon (permanent)
   
0.2.a2 (4.16.12)
 - Added new Mac OS X icon
   
0.2.a1 (4.16.12)
 - Added Mac OS X icon
   
0.2.a0 (4.14.12)
 - Changed the interface from text input to bar input
 - added color rectangle
   
0.1.a1 (4.14.12)
 - Fixed reading number input bug
   
0.1.a0 (4.14.12)
 - text input interface
  